One-third Thank you very much for your time today.
Hello.
Today we have the Kawasaki Brave Thunder Studio.
Now we are going to have a guest appearance at our game.
Yay!
I say guest appearance, but not this way,
I will be performing on the court today,
I'm really, really looking forward to it.
I will do my best for the whole day.
By the way, I'm not very good at basketball.
I like it, but I can't keep dribbling.
Thank you very much for watching.
Thank you for watching!
me
Yes, please do!
Kiccicha
Coolness Kiticha
Soon, isn't it?
It's coming soon!
It's getting hotter and hotter in the hall now.
I mean, the games are heating up.
Oh, here it comes!
It's so cool! It's so cool!
Is this your first time from the venue?
I was able to go and watch a little bit of the game as well.
It's been a long time
It's been a long time.
It's a little bit fun
I'm so happy!
I'm very happy to have such a wonderful opportunity again
I'm very happy and
I hope I can send power to all of you
I will do my best with VV-chan to send power to all of you.
We're also getting even hotter with your enthusiasm.
I'm getting even more passionate!
I'm thinking that you are a wonderful team.
It's a great point of contact, isn't it?
It seems to be a great team.
I'd like to buy one, even if it's just for a glimpse.
Ah!
Oh!
Crab sours are here.
How are you feeling?
The game is heating up.
We'll do our best to raise the excitement at halftime.
I'm going to do my best to get the crowd even more excited at halftime.
Even before the game starts.
They were counting down the minutes before the game started.
Even during the talk show
The players were already practicing in the back.
And the audience, too.
They were really looking forward to the match.
It's a very important match.
We were all a little fired up.
I think they've given us a lot of gifts up to this point.
I'm sure you've been waiting for today.
We hope that everyone will give us their power and work even harder.
We want to give you a performance that will make you work even harder.
I hope we can give you a performance that will give you even more power.
How long have you been doing this?
From the third grade to the third grade of junior high school, so for six years.
But I was very popular.
I was cheering from the bench all the time.
I made a big ink.
I sing.
I love basketball
When I'm happy and when I'm sad
I always feel as one
I'm strong, I'm strong, I'm strong, I'm back, I'm back, I'm serious, I'm serious
I was making that at a senior high school called Byte Height.
That's what I was making
Ditto.
I'm sure you can all hear the sound right now.
I will do my best to make the venue even hotter!
Today, I'm going to sing "Last Chance Last Dance" and "Not Equal Mi".
I will sing "Not Equal Me".
I'll do my best.
Yes, sir.
Now, the next will be. If you want a present, please like it.
I'm going. I'm going. I'll do my best. I'm going. I will help you.
I look forward to working with you.
Thank you very much.
Today, I will be performing at the Kawasaki Brave Santa event.
For this reason, I played basketball at yesterday's talk session.
I am very well prepared.
It's my first time to dance a basketball like this, so I am very nervous.
I was happy to see some fans when I came in.
Let's put our energy into it and do our best to make it exciting.
Let's do our best.
Seino,
Dokidoki!
Let's go for it!
Good luck!
please!
Please, please, please, please.
Please, please, please.
Come on. Come on.
Good luck.
Bye-bye.
This is everyone from Not Equal Me.
It's show time
Thank you for watching
Well
ME.
Let's not let this end like this.
Yeah, right now. Tomorrow's a long way off.
Just as you are, just as you are.
I could live till the end
I could live with the color of your skin.
Your hands on my skin.
I could live till the end.
Summer grass, summer grass, summer grass
Now, blue, the voice of the flowers.
Tear yourself to pieces.
Smile for all the people
On the same stage as always
Baby Sneaking Flowers
This match is one of the most famous high school players in Tokyo Metropolitan University.
He is one of the most famous high school players.
Good night.
Cute!
He hearted me!
Bye-bye.
Thank you.
Andy Asystems.
Yes, that's right.
Full Moon is the B-League's Kawasaki Brave Thunders.
I will be performing in the Huff Time Show at the game!
Thank you very much.
I was just about to put on the last dance
I came to the show when we were about to put on the last dance.
I didn't see a lot of people.
But you are here, and all the players are here.
I am very happy that we had this opportunity for the first time
I was very happy to have this opportunity.
Thank you very much.
I would like to thank all of you who came out for the first time
I hope that those of you who came out for the first time will be able to get a sense of our work
I hope that those of you who have come out for the first time
I hope that our power will be passed on to the players and the audience
I hope that the players and the audience
I hope you will be able to hear what we have to say.
I am glad you are doing well.
Thank you very much for today.
Thank you very much.